{
    "id": "b6e6332297eb4b19a382e22929fb8bed",
    "title": "Reported speech worksheet",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "f5d6ad3503c84d02b3debb7116ecd91e",
            "title": "Reported Speech",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Rahul said that he ............................... fiction.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "likes",
                        "liked",
                        "liking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The girl said that she ....................................... writing a letter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was",
                        "had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy ...................................... that he was waiting for her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "said",
                        "told",
                        "asked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The masons ......................................... that they had finished the job.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "said",
                        "told",
                        "asked"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The boy said that he ...................................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "had selected",
                        "had been selected",
                        "selected"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher asked the girl if she .................................... her homework.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "has done",
                        "had done",
                        "did"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The teacher encouraged the boy ............................................. hard.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "to work",
                        "working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The man said that he .......................................... his bag.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "lost",
                        "has lost",
                        "had lost"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The traveler asked where the nearest inn .......................................",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "is",
                        "was"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I asked him ............................................ he would help me.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "that",
                        "if",
                        "what"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}